Kiley, Dan (Dan Urban), 1912-2004. Papers of Dan Kiley: An Inventory.
Kiley, Dan (Dan Urban), 1912-2004. Papers of Dan Kiley: An Inventory.
- Landscape Architecture Drawings, / Date(s): ca. 1941 - ca. 1995; 0000; / Quantity: ca. 483 tubes; 128 folders; 2 boxes / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
  - Port Douglass & Schuyler Island Development, / Date(s): 1962; Tube: 0515; / Quantity: 2 / Dimensions: <108x85cm. / Medium: Blueline prints / Support: Paper
    Note: Engineer's drawing, together with preliminary perspective drawing.
  - Christian TheologicalSeminary, / Date(s): 1962 - 1976; Tube: 0523; / Quantity: 59 / Dimensions: <148x97cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings and plans developed over more than a decade for various sites on the CTS campus.
    Location of associated materials: See also #1085 - CTS Housing.
  - St. Louis Housing, / Date(s): 1962 - 1963; Tube: 0527; / Quantity: 5 / Dimensions: <108x78cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings and annotated; further information on project unknown.
    Scale: 1"=30'.
  - Pennsylvania Avenue / Pilot Block, / Date(s): 1962 - 1965; Tube: 0528; / Quantity: 31 / Dimensions: <416x108cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings and plans related to scheme for revitalizing a portion of Pennsylvania Avenue.
    Published in: Cf. Dan Kiley: The Complete Works ..., p. 209.
  - Executive Mansion/ Albany, NY, / Date(s): 1962; Tube: 0529; / Quantity: 3 / Dimensions: 99x87cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Tracing vellum
    Note: Alternative scheme for grounds of the Executive Mansion at Albany.
    Note: Following a fire in 1961, gubernatorial brother-in-law Wallace K. Harrison oversaw repairs and restoration of house and grounds.
  - Goddard Riverside Community Center, / Date(s): 1962 - 1966; Tube: 0530; / Quantity: 17 / Dimensions: <127x99cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Preliminary, schematic and working drawings.
  - White Mountain Development / Kilkenny, / Date(s): 1968; Tube: 0534; / Quantity: 7 / Dimensions: <160x105cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Annotated prints in a variety of media.
    Scale: 1"=600'.
  - E Street / Washington, D.C., / Date(s): 1962; Tube: 0535; / Quantity: 47 / Dimensions: <165x67cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Presentation and working drawings for improvements on Washington's E Street, between 20th and 23rd Streets.
  - Oakland Museum, / Date(s): 1962ca. - 1967; Tube: 0536; / Quantity: 44 / Dimensions: <48"x36" / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings and plans, draswn up over an extended period, focused on the Oakland Museum grounds, with special emphasis on its complex terrace plantings.
    Note: The file includes photocopies of original notes and sketches.
  - Quinnipiac School, / Date(s): 1962; Tube: 0537; / Quantity: 9 / Dimensions: 94 x 64cm. / Medium: Ink;pencil / Support: Tracing vellum
    Note: Plans for elementary school property.
    Location of associated materials: Yale University (Mss. & Archives) holds slides documenting construction of school.
  - Hamilton-Cosco Company, / Date(s): 1962; Tube: 0539; / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings and plans in a variety of media.
  - Neiman Marcus Shopping Center, / Date(s): 1962; Tube: 0540; / Quantity: 4 / Dimensions: 109x79cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Annotated prints in a mix of media.
    Note: Landscape plans for Neiman Marcus Fort Worth store; building designed by Edward Larrabee Barnes, 1961.
  - Wrexham Foundation/Manuscript [Society], / Date(s): 1962; Tube: 0541; / Quantity: 4 / Dimensions: <87x54cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Landscape plans for grounds of Manuscript Society (one of Yale's private student clubs), funded by the Wrexham Trust.
    Note: The clubhouse, designed by King Lui Wu, has been unkindly described as a "tiny modernist shack".
  - Emma Willard School, / Date(s): 1962; Tube: 0542; / Quantity: 11 / Dimensions: <175x107cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings and plans related to the Emma Willard campus; architect Edward L/ Barnes was involved in several projects at the school in this period.
  - Art Institute of Chicago / South Garden, / Date(s): 1963 - 1966; Tube: 0546; / Quantity: 39 / Dimensions: <108 x 92cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Materials related to one of the best-known Kiley designs; drawings span a three-year period.
    Published in: Cf. Dan Kiley The Complete Works..., pp.48-53.
    Published in: Among the numerous journal articles devoted to the Art Institute is: "A Man for All Seasons",The Inland Architect, July/August 1993.
  - Burr McManus Memorial Park, / Date(s): 1967 - 1970; Tube: 0547; / Quantity: 15 / Dimensions: <108x77cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Preliminary and working drawings, dating from 1967-1970, accompanied by set of blueline prints from the office of CR3, dated 1990.
    Note: The Kiley landscape for this site has been demolished.
  - University of Vermont / Votey Engineering Building, / Date(s): 1963; Tube: 0553; / Quantity: 6 / Dimensions: <106x84cm. / Medium: Pencil;ink; sepia print / Support: Paper
    Note: Plans related to grounds of Votey Engineering Building, constructed in 1963 at the UV Burlington campus.
  - State University of New York at Potsdam, / Date(s): 1963; Tube: 0555; / Quantity: 37 / Dimensions: <180x108cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings in a variety of media, related to grounds of library, student union and classroom buildings.
    Location of associated materials: See also #0555 and #729.
  - John Wilkie Residence, / Date(s): 1955 - 1963; Tube: 0558; / Quantity: 8 / Dimensions: <149x97cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings and sketches accompanied by survey plan dated 1955.
  - James Barton Elliott Residence, / Date(s): 1963; Tube: 0560; / Quantity: 1 / Dimensions: 90x74cm. / Medium: Pencil / Support: Tracing paper
    Note: Identified as "Preliminary Planting Plan."
  - Grant Park / Chicago, / Date(s): 1963; Tube: 0563; / Quantity: 9 / Dimensions: <169x107cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Tracing paper
    Note: Preliminary plans for one of several Chicago park projects.
    Location of associated materials: Cf. #636 "South Michigan Avenue", and #546 "Art Institute."
  - Wadi Sawabini Residence, / Date(s): 1963; Tube: 0565; / Quantity: 2 / Dimensions: <91x61cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Preliminary drawing and annotated site plan.
  - State University of New York at Fredonia, / Date(s): 1963; Tube: 0570; / Quantity: 51 / Dimensions: <156x112cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings related to improvements to a number of sites on the Fredonia campus; Pei Cobb Freed were the principal architects.
    Published in: CF. THE COMPLETE WORKS ..., pp. 209-210.
  - Clarence Hamilton Residence, / Date(s): 1963 - 1972; Tube: 0573; / Quantity: 18 / Dimensions: <107x117cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings, in mixed media, date through 1972.
    Published in: Published in: "When Design Compels", Landscape Architecture, Autumn 1986., pp. 64-69.
    Published in: Cf. THE COMPLETE WORKS ..., p. 205.
  - George Newlin Residence, / Date(s): 1963; Tube: 0575; / Quantity: 10 / Dimensions: <95x63 cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Preliminary and working drawings; house designed by Harry Weese.
  - Atlas Crankshaft, / Date(s): 1963 - 1976; Tube: 0578; / Quantity: 9 / Dimensions: <71x81cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Plans in mixed media, extendng over a 13-year period.
  - Kenneth Dayton Residence, / Date(s): 1963; Tube: 0579; / Quantity: 36 / Dimensions: <132x108cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mylar
    Note: Plans and drawings relatedf to the Dayton property.
    Location of associated materials: Cf. #438, "Dayton Residence" (1957).,
  - National Academy of Sciences / 22nd Street Entrance, / Date(s): 1962 - 1963; Tube: 0581; / Quantity: 3 / Dimensions: 96x30cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Tracing vellum
    Note: Working drawings focused on 22nd Street entrance to the Academy.
    Location of associated materials: Cf. #437 and #638 for other National Academy of Sciences projects.
  - State University of New York College of Environmental Science and Forestry, / Date(s): 1963; Tube: 0582; / Quantity: 12 / Dimensions: <137x78cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings related to the former College of Forestry site at Syracuse.
  - University of Vermont / Campus Plan, / Date(s): 1963 - 197-?; Tube: 0583; / Quantity: 59 / Dimensions: <171x109cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Campus planning materials dating from 1963 into the 1970s.
  - Armstrong Cork Company, / Date(s): 1964; Tube: 0586; / Quantity: 1 / Dimensions: 105x148cm. / Medium: Ink / Support: Mylar
    Note: Master/site plan for corporate headquarters.
    Note: "Armstrong Cork" now Armstrong Holdings, Inc.
  - Central District Filtration Plant / Chicago, / Date(s): 1964; Tube: 0589; / Quantity: 10 / Dimensions: <124x88cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Identified as "Competition" in ODK project list.
    Location of associated materials: Cf. #1273, "Navy Pier Reconstruction".
    Published in: Cf. COMPLETE WORKS ..., pp. 36 -39.
  - Columbus Community Schools, / Date(s): 1964 - 1965; Tube: 0591; / Quantity: 49 / Dimensions: <115x105cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings file includes site and planting plans for both schools' grounds.
    Published in: For an introduction to the architecture and landscape architecture of Columbus, cf. Columbus, Indiana: A Look at the Architecture (1984) and Colmbus, Indiana: An American Landmark (1989).
  - Cummins Engine Company / Darlington Plant, / Date(s): 1964; Tube: 0592; / Quantity: 1 / Dimensions: 174x82cm. / Medium: Sepia print / Support: Paper
    Note: Plating plan (with architect's floor plan) for Cummings plant; structure designed by Dinkeloo and Roche.
    Scale: 1"=16'.
    Published in: For further information, cf. www site "Risky Buildings."
  - Columbus Country Club / Otter Creek, / Date(s): 1964; Tube: 0593; / Quantity: 5 / Dimensions: <94x64cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Alternate site and plantig plan studies for golf course and clubhouse (latter designed by Harry Weese).
    Note: A gift to the City of Columbus in 1964 by the Cummins Engine Company, the facility was named the "Otter Creek Clubhouse and Golf Course."
    Note: The golf course itself was designed by Robert Trent Jones and Rees L. Jones.
  - Cummins Research Laboratory, / Date(s): 1964 - 1974; Tube: 0594; / Quantity: 14 / Dimensions: <118x83cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings for Cummins Research Laboratory grounds; laboratory designed by Harry Weese.
    Published in: For an introduction to the architecture and landscape architecture of Cuolumbus, IN, cf. Columbus, Indiana: A Look at the Architecture(1984) and Columbus, Indiana, an American Landmark(1989).
  - Experiment in International Living, / Date(s): 1964; Tube: 0596; / Quantity: 43 / Dimensions: <110x80cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Sepia prints, annotated in pencil of drawings for residences for EIL Director and President.
    Note: Precise location uncertain; plans indicate Putney; organization based in Brattleboro.
    Location of associated materials: Cf. #677. Experiment in International Living/Library.
  - FAA Traffic Control Towers, / Date(s): 1964; Tube: 0597; / Quantity: 6 / Dimensions: 92x61cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Pei Cobb Freed designed some 50 air traffic control towers for the FAA from ca. 1962-1972, located at cities in the US and abroad.
    Note: This file includes Kiley designs for four unidentified locations.
  - State University of New York at Fredonia / President's House, / Date(s): 1964; Tube: 0599; / Quantity: 3 / Dimensions: <110x83cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings in a variety of states and media.
    Note: Despite the citation of I.M. Pei as architect in Dan Kiley: The Complete Works ..., the President's House is attributed to Noah D. Snow and was built in the mid-1850s.
    Note: One assumes the Pei citation is a reference to the Master Plan for the campus devised by Pei Cobb Freed.
    Published in: CF. THE COMPLETE WORKS..., pp. 209-210.
  - State University of New York at Fredonia/Dormitories, / Date(s): 1964 - 1967; Tube: 0600; / Quantity: 9 / Dimensions: <149x93cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings (including contract drawings) related to the S1 and S7 dormitories. The names assigned these structures have changed over the years.
  - State University of New York at Fredonia/ Dormitories/ S11, / Date(s): 1964 - 1968; Tube: 0601; / Quantity: 32 / Dimensions: <213x92cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Content: Drawings include Stages XI and XIII and include drawings related to infirmary.
  - Ford Foundation, / Date(s): 1964 - 1965; Tube: 0602; / Quantity: 72 / Dimensions: <129x107cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings include preliminary studies and a variety of prints and check set.
    Published in: Cf. Dan Kiley: The Complete Works, pp. 66-67; and "A Foundation's Atelier", Industrial Design, March 1968, pp. 26-27.
  - IBM/ Milwaukee, / Date(s): 1964; Tube: 0605; / Quantity: 6 / Dimensions: 107x78m. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: ODK drawings in ink and pencil accompanied by blueline architectural prints.
  - Edward Janeway Residence, / Date(s): 1964; Tube: 0606; / Quantity: 1 / Dimensions: 100x67cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Tracing vellum
    Note: Location not indicated; most probably a design for Vermont State Senator Edward Janeway, leading developer of Stratton Mountain.
  - Irwin Union Bank & Trust Company, / Date(s): 1964 - 1968; Tube: 0607; / Quantity: 7 / Dimensions: <116x86cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Planting plans for structure designed by Saarinen in 1954.
    Published in: Cf.Dan Kiley: The Complete Works ..., p. 211.
  - North Christian Church, / Date(s): 1964 - 1974; Tube: 0608; / Quantity: 10 / Dimensions: <200x108cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings in ink and pencil on vellum and sepia prints.
    Note: Also included are drawings for additional planting and parking, dated 1971-1974, together with print of architect's site plan.
    Note: Designed by Eero Saarinen, the church was built and completed by his successor firm,
  - North Elementary School, / Date(s): 1964; Tube: 0610; / Quantity: 1 / Dimensions: <131x93cm. / Medium: Pencil; ink / Support: Paper
    Note: Annotated sepia prints of planting plans and details.
    Note: North Elementary is now known as W.D. Richards Elementary School.
    Note: Jaquelin Robertson identified as Project Architect in Edward Larrabee Barnes: Architect ..., p. 241.
  - Putnam Residence, / Date(s): 1964; Tube: 0611; / Quantity: 21 / Dimensions: <77x64cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Client's first name and additional information lacking.
  - St. Louis Community College at Forest Park, / Date(s): 1964 - 1967; Tube: 0612; / Quantity: 6 / Dimensions: <117x109cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings, in mixed media, date over several years.
  - Rockefeller University - South, / Date(s): 1964; Tube: 0613; / Quantity: 12 / Dimensions: <127x99cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: These materials date from the mid-60s, a decade after the expansion of the research facility.
    Location of associated materials: Cf. #424, "Rockefeller Institute", #883 "Tower Parking Lot" and #931, "Tower Building-Plaza."
    Published in: Cf. Elizabeth Hanson, The Rockefeller University Achievement ... (200).
  - St. Paul's School, / Date(s): 1961 - 1966; Tube: 0614; / Quantity: 35 / Dimensions: <152x108cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings related to this collaborative master planning project undertaken with Edward L. Barnes.
    Published in: Cf. Dan Kiley: The Complete Works, p. 210.
  - University of Vermont / Life Sciences Building, / Date(s): 1964; Tube: 0617; / Quantity: 6 / Dimensions: <107x78cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Sketches and annotated prints in a variety of media.
  - University of Minnesota/Duluth Campus, / Date(s): 1964; Tube: 0619; / Quantity: 2 / Dimensions: 106x78cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Tracing vellum
    Note: Mixed media on trace.
    Note: The Minneapolis office of Close Associates is credited for both the Duluth and West Bank plans by the University of Minnesota.
    Location of associated materials: cf. #621, University of Minnesota, Minneapolis campus.
  - University of Minnesota / West Bank Campus, / Date(s): 1964; Tube: 0621; / Quantity: 6 / Dimensions: <99x79cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings in mixed media. The Minneapolis firm of Close Associates is credited with the design for this and the Duluth campus by the University.
    Location of associated materials: Cf. #619, University of Minnesota, Duluth campus.
  - New Haven Parks / West River Memorial and Edgewood, / Date(s): 1966; Tube: 0625; / Quantity: 28 / Dimensions: <167x108cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Original drawings for two New Haven parks, part of a larger group of municipal recreation areas.
  - State University of New York at Fredonia / Dormitories /S9, / Date(s): 1965 - 1969; Tube: 0634; / Quantity: 18 / Dimensions: <150x90cm.> / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Original drawings and annotated prints, dated from 1965-1969.
  - State University of New York at Fredonia / S2 and Ring Road, / Date(s): 1965; Tube: 0635; / Quantity: 9 / Dimensions: 152x85cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings for arterial road include Student Union and Academic Center.
  - South Michigan Avenue, / Date(s): 1965 - 1970; Tube: 0636; / Quantity: 12 / Dimensions: <370x57cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings and plans in a variety of formats, generated over a five-year period.
    Location of associated materials: Cf. #546, Art Institute of Chicago and #563.
  - National Academy of Sciences / Courtyard, / Date(s): 1963 - 1964; Tube: 0638; / Quantity: 6 / Dimensions: <107x88cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings in a variety of formats, dated 1963-1964; job realized in 1965.
    Location of associated materials: Cf. #437, National Academy ... Constitution Avenue.. and #581, National Academy ... 22nd St.
  - Euclid Avenue / University Circle, / Date(s): 1965; Tube: 0646; / Quantity: 14 / Dimensions: <161x95cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Plans and drawings in a variety of formats, focused on this important cultural district in Cleveland.
    Note: Client or sponsor not indicated.
  - University of Vermont / North Campus, / Date(s): 1965; Tube: 0650; / Quantity: 13 / Dimensions: <161x108cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings and prints, in various media.
  - Virginia Avenue, / Date(s): 1965; Tube: 0653; / Quantity: 15 / Dimensions: <393x108cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Identified in file as "Contract 1". Drawings and prints, together with aerial photograph.
  - Burlington City Hall Park, / Date(s): 1965; Tube: 0655; / Quantity: 5 / Dimensions: <119x85cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: File includes contour and tree location plan, with topographic surveys.
    Note: Termed a "Prospective" in Dan Kiley: The Complete Works ..., p.210.
    Scale: 1"=10'; topos are 1"=20'.
  - Chicago Teachers Union / Apartments, / Date(s): 1965; Tube: 0656; / Quantity: 13 / Dimensions: <108x83cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: File includes drawings from ODK as well as prints of from the office of the architect, Harry Weese.
  - First Baptist Church / Columbus, Indiana, / Date(s): 1965 - 1966; Tube: 0657; / Quantity: 3 / Dimensions: 93x61cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Plans for grounds of church designed by Harry Weese.
  - Herald Tribune Fresh Air Fund Camp, / Date(s): 1965; Tube: 0659; / Quantity: 2 / Dimensions: 80x57cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Tracing vellum
    Note: Site plans; long-time Kiley collaborator Edward L. Barnes had also been associated with site.
  - IBM / Armonk, / Date(s): 1965; Tube: 0660; / Quantity: 7 / Dimensions: 112x108cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Landscape plans for the IBM Armonk facility; the firm moved its headquarters from Manhattan in 1964.
  - Milwaukee Center for the Performing Arts, / Date(s): 1965 - 1966; Tube: 0661; / Quantity: 3 / Dimensions: 128x93cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Preliminary drawings from ODK; structure designed by Harry Weese and completed in 1969.
    Note: Originally known as Milwaukee Center for the Performing Arts.
    Location of associated materials: Cf. #733, Marcus Center for the Performing Arts
  - Thrall Car Manufacturing Company, / Date(s): 1965; Tube: 0663; / Quantity: 6 / Dimensions: 108x78cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: ODK office list identifies architect as Harry Weese.
    Note: Thrall, a leading manufacturer of railroad cars, eventually merged (2001) with Trinity Industries.
  - Kenwood Housing, / Date(s): 1965; Tube: 0666; / Quantity: 1 / Dimensions: 170x66cm. / Medium: Blueline print / Support: Paper
    Note: File includes only preliminary site plan from the Weese office.
    Scale: 1/64"=1'.
  - Alta-Snowbird Ski Development, / Date(s): 1966; Tube: 0671; / Quantity: 9 / Dimensions: <117x194cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Material related to preliminary development plans for the Snowbird resort area in the mid-1960s.
    Published in: Cf. Dan Kiley: The Complete Works..., p.211.
  - Carleton College, / Date(s): 1966; Tube: 0673; / Quantity: 31 / Dimensions: <200x108cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Preliminary drawings and other materials related to campus plan.
    Location of associated materials: Cf. #770, Carleton College--Phase I.
  - Chicago Public Works / S-SW Interchange, / Date(s): 1966; Tube: 0675; / Quantity: 3 / Dimensions: <200x108cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Drawings in mixed media.
  - Experiment in International Living / Library, / Date(s): 1966; Tube: 0677; / Quantity: 15 / Dimensions: <109x88cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Architectural plans for EIIL library.
    Location of associated materials: Cf. #596, Experiment in International Living.
  - Yale University / Jonathan Edwards College, / Date(s): 1966; Tube: 0678; / Quantity: 11 / Dimensions: <94x65cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Tracing paper
    Note: Drawings for the "Master's Garden" of the Yale residential college.
  - Ottauquechee River Study, / Date(s): 1966; Tube: 0679; / Quantity: 32 / Dimensions: <206x107cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Material related to a study, sponsored by Laurence Rockefeller, focused on issues of conservation and land use in the Ottauquechee watershed.
    Note: File includes survey plans and drawings.
    Published in: Cf. Dan Kiley: The Complete Works ..., p. 211.
  - New Haven Parks / East Shore Park, / Date(s): 1966; Tube: 0681; / Quantity: 3 / Dimensions: <112x82cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: Site plans and perspective drawings for this New Haven park, situated on the harbor.
    Location of associated materials: Cf. #682, #684, #686.
  - New Haven Parks / Edgerton Gardens, / Date(s): 1966; Tube: 0682; / Quantity: 13 / Dimensions: <126x108cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
    Note: A miscellany of plans and drawings related to this ara (now called Edgerton Park); it became part of the New Haven park system in 1965.
    Location of associated materials: Cf. #681, #684, #686.
  - New Haven Parks / Lighthouse Point Park, / Date(s): 1966; Tube: 0684; / Quantity: 11 / Dimensions: <112x96cm. / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed